[SINGING] Designing emails can be really tough.
在設計 郵件 可真 難熬。
Client preprocessors can be pretty rough.
客戶端 預處理器 可以是相當 粗糙。
To code email for all their devices,
編寫 電子郵件 的 所有設備 ，
cut the design into many slices.
切 設計 成很多 片。
Mark it up in tables with inline style,
與 內嵌樣式 表 標記 起來 ，
with media queries into one big file.
有 媒體查詢 成一個大文件 。
To win, you'll train and learn the details —
要贏， 你會 訓練和 學習 的細節 - 。
Unmasking HTML Emails!
揭露 HTML 電子郵件！
Welcome back.
歡迎回來。
This is level four, and in this level,
這 是 第四階段 ，在這裡
we're going to have a few rematches with prior opponents.
我們將要重新面對之前的幾個困難。
They've learned your tricks, so you're going to have to come up with some new skills.
他們已經看穿了你的技巧 ，所以你不得不拿出一些新的技能。
We're going to use conditional styles, conditional content,and learn how to counter some client features.
我們將使用條件樣式，有條件的內容，並學習如何應對一些客戶端的功能。
We know that Word-based rendering engines have issues.
我們知道，文字排版引擎有些問題。
Now we're going to focus in on correcting a few of them.
現在我們將集中注意力在解決這些問題上。
We can see that our text is too big in Outlook 2007 and in Outlook 2010, as well as having multiple line height issues in both clients.
我們可以看到，在outlook 2007和2010中有文字過大和多行顯示的問題。
Taking a look at one of their teammates, Outlook 2013,
在來看看他們另一個版本，Outlook 2013
we can see that it has some of those issues,but not all of them
雖然不是全部，但我們還是可以看到一些問題。
and then adds additional issues where line height is being applied differently to a border and images.
有一些額外的問題，行高被應用在不同的邊框和圖像上。
We need a way to target individual Outlook clients,
我們需要個別的方法來針對個別的Outlook客戶端 ，
and lucky for us, there are conditional comments.
幸運的是我們還有"條件註釋"可以用。
The simplest conditional comment that we will use targets all versions of Microsoft Outlook.
最簡單的"條件註釋"，我們將會應用在所有版本的Microsoft Outlook中。
If we want to target specific versions,
如果我們要針對特定版本，
we can use operators,like this GTE operator that
我們可以使用運算子，像GTE這樣的運算符
checks for all versions of Outlook that are greater than or equal to version 12.
用來檢查所有版本的outlook是大於還是等於第12版本。
We can use the conditional comments to fix the font problems.
我們可以使用"條件註釋"來修復字體的問題。
We are having problems with Outlook 2007 and 2010.
在outlook2007和outlook2010上有問題。
We're going to use an operator to target Microsoft Outlook greater than or equal to version 12,and less than version 15.
我們將使用運算式去判斷Microsoft Outlook的版本是大於等於12和小於15。
This gives us our versions 2007 and 2010.
這為我們提供了2007年 和2010年的版本。
Inside our new conditional comment,
我們的新條件註釋裡面，
we're going to redefine our email slogan class,
我們要重新定義你的電子郵件標題 class，
and apply properties necessary to get that text on one line.
並運用必要屬性來讓文字顯示在同一行 。
Versions of Microsoft Outlook that use Word as a rendering engine render line height differently than browsers.
文字的行高，在使用Word為排版引擎的Microsoft Outlook版本中，是不同於瀏覽器的。
It's almost like they knew this,
這幾乎就像他們知道這一點，
because they added a vendor-specific property
因為他們增加了一個內建特定的屬性，
that we can use to tell Word to set our line height exactly to pixel values.
可以用它來告訴Word用像素值來精確設置你的行高。
We're going to use a conditional comment
我們將使用條件註釋
to target all versions of Outlook using Microsoft Word as the rendering engine,
來讓所有版本的Outlook都是使用Microsoft Word 作為排版引擎
and apply this property to table cells.
且將這個主性應用到表格單元格 。
Here, you can see that our line height has improved on our email titles.
現在 ， 你可以看到這行電子郵件的標題高度已經被改進了
Now that we have our line height looking good,
現在 ，我們已經讓行高看起來不錯，
we can use that same conditional comment to add properties
我們可以用同樣的條件註釋來添加屬性 。
and reduce padding on specific text areas.
並減少在文本區域的留白
We're going to set the padding bottom of our email title to zero to trim up that space.
我們要設置電子郵件的標題下方和本文是沒有距離的。
Because we use this vendor property
因為我們使用該內建屬性 。
and set our cell's line height to 14 pixels,
並設置我們的單元格高度為14像素，
that affects all of the text within the cell.
這影響文中所有的單元格。
This property is not supported on inline elements,
這個屬性不支持行內元素，
so we can't apply it to our spans.
因此 ，我們不能將其應用到我們的spans
Instead, we need to change our line height to accommodate all of the text within the cell.
相反，我們需要改變我們的行高，以適應所有內文中的單元表格。
We would do this by grabbing the highest value, which,in this case, is 32 pixels.
我們將抓取最大的數值，如這例子中是32pixels
Now that we know the size to use, we can create a class
現在我們知道使用的大小， 我們 可以創建一個類別
and apply that to the table cells.
並應用到表格單元格 。
We fixed all of our line heights or text,
我們修復了所有我們的行高或文字，
but there's an unusual case in Outlook 2013 with empty cells.
但有一個不尋常的情況下，在 Outlook 2013 的空單元格 。
If a cell is empty, Outlook ignores the height.
如果單元格是空的 ， Outlook就會忽略行高。
This doesn't require conditional comments or fixing.
這並不需要有條件的設定或固定。
We just need to add a non- breaking space in there for Outlook to recognize the height.
我們只需要在裡面添加一個non- breaking空間讓Outlook知道高度。
Outlook 2013 also has some weird things
Outlook 2013 也有一些 奇怪的事情 。
in the way it treats line height for images.
在設定圖片的行高上
To correct this, we need to treat images like they were text,
要糾正這一點，我們需要像文字一般的設定圖像
and apply a font size and line height that's equal to the height of the image.
並應用字體大小和等於圖像高度的行高
If we look at our email in Outlook using Internet Explorer and Outlook using Word,
如果我們看一下在使用IE排版引擎和word排版引擎的Outlook中的電子郵件。
we have a very consistent experience.
我們有一個非常一致的體驗。
Now it's your turn to use conditional styles in the challenges.
現在 輪到你 在挑戰中使用 條件樣式 。